here's an interesting Pi conundrum start
with a semicircle with radius one so
that it has a circumference of Pi now we
can draw two semicircles inside each has
a radius of a half so has a
circumference of pi/ 2 for a combined
length of Pi again now draw two
semicircles in each of those semicircles
so that each has a radius of 1/4 and a
circumference of pi over 4 for a
combined total length of Pi again we can
continue this process over and over
again each time we double the number of
semicircles but we have the radius this
means that the total combined lengths of
their circumferences will always remain
pi as we keep doing this we see that the
semicircles squash down and flattened to
almost match the diameter of the
original semicircle does that mean that
the length of the diameter of the
original semicircle is actually equal to
Pi when we consider the limiting process
is pi equal to 2 of course Pi isn't
equal to two but can you see where this
argument fails